http://www.dsource.org/site/privacy

Note: This website is archived.
For up-to-date information about D projects and development, please visit
wiki.dlang.org.
DSOURCE.ORG PRIVACY STATEMENT
dsource.org is committed to protecting the privacy of users of our site. At dsource.org, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information, including the registration data. As part of the normal operation of this site, we collect information from you. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.
INFORMATION GATHERED THROUGH THE DSOURCE.ORG WEB SITE:
dsource.org will track the domains from which people visit dsource.org and analyze this data for trends and statistics. Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, dsource.org may use accumulated data for various purposes, including but not limited to marketing analysis, service evaluation and planning.
Currently, dsource.org uses personal information as a basis for notifications to users, "opt-in" emails, and in order to implement the terms of the Terms of Service governing the website (the "Terms"). User names and email addresses (as well as any additional information that a user may choose to post) are publicly available on the dsource.org site. When users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information that may contain Registration Data, or otherwise post personal information in conjunction with content subject to an Open Source license, such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the terms of the license. An example of such a disclosure includes, but is not limited to, a user's disclosure of personal information as part of a message posted to a public message forum, or a publicly-released software application.
dsource.org may conduct surveys of other studies of its customer base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and dsource.org will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where dsource.org advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, dsource.org reserves the right to disclose text information provided by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option; dsource.org does not conduct mandatory surveys. Circumstances under which dsource.org would publicly disclose such aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population, providing data to dsource.org advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications.
Cookies: dsource.org employs "cookies" to provide a user with tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that a Service or site, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser that, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory. dsource.org uses cookies to better serve users who use our Services; any cookies sent by dsource.org will be marked so that they will be accessible only by websites subject to this Privacy Statement. However, at his or her option, and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. By disabling cookies, however, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.
Other Notification: In order to implement or enforce the Terms of dsource.org, dsource.org may use personal information to contact users on an individual basis.
At no time, unless law requires such disclosure, disclosure is necessary to aid law enforcement, or a user specifically authorizes such disclosure, will dsource.org disclose individual user personal information that is not publicly available to unrelated third parties.
LINKS WITH OTHER SITES
dsource.org contains links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by dsource.org affiliates or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of dsource.org. dsource.org is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit.
CHOICE
"Opt-in" Emails: Users may "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions.
Profile Display: In some cases, users' personal information may be publicly available through a user's profile display.
In such cases, users have the option to opt out of publicly displaying their real names. In cases where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at the user's discretion and may be changed at any time by the user.
Email Display: In some cases, users may have the opportunity to use a Service to send electronic mail to another user or email list. In such cases, a user's valid email address and real name will be included with such messages. In order to prevent abuse, users may not opt-out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from using said Service to transmit an email message.
ACCESS
Users can view their data on their personal profile page. When technically feasible, users are permitted to update their personal information directly through dsource.org Service. When such updating service is not technically feasible, dsource.org will make reasonable efforts to assist users in updating their personal information.
SECURITY
To secure site integrity, dsource.org employs measures including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures.
Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis.
ENFORCEMENT
In the event that dsource.org becomes aware that site security is compromised or user nonpublic information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, dsource.org shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Statement.
If dsource.org becomes aware that a user's personal information provided to dsource.org has been disclosed in a manner not permitted by this Privacy Statement, dsource.org shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that dsource.org knows this information.
UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY STATEMENT
To substantively update the Privacy Statement, we will both post the changed version and its effective date at http://www.dsource.org/site/privacy. Concurrently with any substantive change to the Privacy Statement, we will email notice of the change to known users at least 15 days in advance (or such shorter or longer time as mandated by law or any judicial or government body).
Text last modified on July 6, 2004.
NO GUARANTEES
While this Privacy Statement expresses dsource.org's standards for maintenance of private data, dsource.org is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, dsource.org disclaims any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of private information.
back to Site Home
Download in other formats:Plain TextPlain TextPlain Text
© Copyright 2004-2020 - The Sankaty Group, Inc.
All rights reserved.
Make a Donation
Privacy Statement
Terms of Service
